<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rachel Melo</title>
    <link>http://rachelmds.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Rachel Melo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 16:43:17 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://rachelmds.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>  Adventure</title>
      <link>http://rachelmds.com/projects/adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 20:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rachelmds.com/projects/adventure/</guid>
      <description>An art tribute to the movie Up!, by Pixar Animation Studios. Used Adobe Photoshop.
Homenagem ao filme Up! - Altas Aventuras, do estúdio Pixar Animation Studios. Foi utilizado o software Adobe Photoshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bom tempo</title>
      <link>http://rachelmds.com/projects/bom-tempo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 20:29:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rachelmds.com/projects/bom-tempo/</guid>
      <description>Original character developed for a college project with sustainability as the main theme. Used Adobe Illustrator for vectorization and Adobe Photoshop for coloring.
Personagem original criada para um projeto de faculdade com sustentabilidade como tema principal. Foram utilizados os softwares Adobe Illustrator para vetorização e Adobe Photoshop para colorização.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Allons-y</title>
      <link>http://rachelmds.com/projects/allons-y/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 20:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rachelmds.com/projects/allons-y/</guid>
      <description>Fanart from the BBC series Doctor Who. Used Adobe Photoshop.
Fanart da série da BBC Doctor Who. Feito no Photoshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Turnabout</title>
      <link>http://rachelmds.com/projects/first-turnabout/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 20:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rachelmds.com/projects/first-turnabout/</guid>
      <description>An art tribute to the game Phoenix Wright Ace Attorney by Capcom. Used Adobe Illustrator for vectoring and Adobe Photoshop for coloring.
Homenagem ao jogo Phoenix Wright Ace Attorney da empresa Capcom. Foram utilizados os softwares Adobe Illustrator para vetorização e Adobe Photoshop para colorização.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bear Hug</title>
      <link>http://rachelmds.com/projects/bear-hug/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 20:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rachelmds.com/projects/bear-hug/</guid>
      <description>Exercise done in Adobe Photoshop.
Exercício feito no Adobe Photoshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cobogó</title>
      <link>http://rachelmds.com/projects/cobog%C3%B3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 20:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rachelmds.com/projects/cobog%C3%B3/</guid>
      <description>Promotional posters created for my graduation group project for college. Used Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Illustrator.
Pôsteres promocionais criados para o trabalho de conclusão de curso da faculdade (projeto feito em grupo). Foram utilizados os softwares Adobe Photoshop e Adobe Illustrator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BNP Paribas brochure</title>
      <link>http://rachelmds.com/projects/bnp-paribas-brochure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 20:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rachelmds.com/projects/bnp-paribas-brochure/</guid>
      <description>Editorial work for a corporate brochure used to present the institution to clients. Used Adobe InDesign for layout and text formatting.
Trabalho editorial para um folder institucional usado para apresentar a instituição a clientes. Foi utilizado o software Adobe InDesign para o layout e editoração do folder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hobbit &#43; Miss Peregrine’s Home for Peculiar Children</title>
      <link>http://rachelmds.com/projects/books01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 18:25:35 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rachelmds.com/projects/books01/</guid>
      <description>Editorial work for a college project in which I redesigned the text formatting (including stylistic choices) for the books “The Hobbit” by JRR Tolkien, and “Ms. Peregrine’s Home for Peculiar Children” by Ramsom Riggs. The illustration for this project was made by a classmate. Used Adobe InDesign.
Trabalho editorial para um projeto da faculdade no qual rediagramei os livros “O Hobbit” por JRR Tolkien e “O Orfanato da Srta. Peregrine para Crianças Peculiares” por Ramson Riggs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Invention of Morel</title>
      <link>http://rachelmds.com/projects/books02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 15:47:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rachelmds.com/projects/books02/</guid>
      <description>Editorial work for a college project in which I designed a cover of the book The Invention of Morel, by Adolfo Bioy Casares. I also redesigned the text formatting of the entire book, and was responsible for its printing as well. Used Adobe Illustration for the artwork and Adobe InDesign for text formatting.
Trabalho editorial para um projeto da faculdade no qual eu fiz um design da capa do livro A Invenção de Morel, por Adolfo Bioy Casares.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>